import { MCQuestionType, TFQuestionType } from "../types";

export const mediumMC: MCQuestionType[] = [
  {
    question: "Who is known as 'The Worm' due to his rebounding skills?",
    choices: ["Dennis Rodman", "Kevin Garnett", "Chris Bosh", "Pau Gasol"],
    correct: "Dennis Rodman",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most assists in a single NBA game with 30 assists?",
    choices: ["John Stockton", "Magic Johnson", "Chris Paul", "Rajon Rondo"],
    correct: "Scott Skiles",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the youngest player in NBA history to score 70 or more points in a single game?",
    choices: ["LeBron James", "Kevin Durant", "Devin Booker", "Kobe Bryant"],
    correct: "Devin Booker",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA team drafted Dirk Nowitzki before he was traded to the Dallas Mavericks?",
    choices: [
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
    ],
    correct: "Milwaukee Bucks",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for the most steals in a single NBA season?",
    choices: [
      "Chris Paul",
      "John Stockton",
      "Alvin Robertson",
      "Michael Jordan",
    ],
    correct: "Alvin Robertson",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA team drafted Kobe Bryant before he was traded to the Los Angeles Lakers?",
    choices: [
      "Charlotte Hornets",
      "Vancouver Grizzlies",
      "Toronto Raptors",
      "Golden State Warriors",
    ],
    correct: "Charlotte Hornets",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player won the NBA MVP award for the 2010-2011 season?",
    choices: ["LeBron James", "Derrick Rose", "Kevin Durant", "Stephen Curry"],
    correct: "Derrick Rose",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA player was nicknamed 'The Admiral'?",
    choices: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "David Robinson",
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      "Patrick Ewing",
    ],
    correct: "David Robinson",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA team has won the most consecutive championships, with eight in a row from 1959 to 1966?",
    choices: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Detroit Pistons",
    ],
    correct: "Boston Celtics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the first player to be drafted directly from high school into the NBA in 1995?",
    choices: ["Kobe Bryant", "LeBron James", "Kevin Garnett", "Tracy McGrady"],
    correct: "Kevin Garnett",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA team won their first NBA Championship in 2019?",
    choices: [
      "Toronto Raptors",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Cleveland Cavaliers",
      "Houston Rockets",
    ],
    correct: "Toronto Raptors",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA player below has won both an MVP and Sixth Man of the Year?",
    choices: ["Bill Walton", "David Cowens", "Derrick Rose", "Bob McAdoo"],
    correct: "Bill Walton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA player holds the record for most points scored in a playoff game?",
    choices: [
      "Elgin Baylor",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "LeBron James",
    ],
    correct: "Michael Jordan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA team has the longest active playoff appearance streak?",
    choices: [
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
    ],
    correct: "San Antonio Spurs",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA team was the first to win back-to-back championships in the 1950s?",
    choices: [
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Minneapolis Lakers",
    ],
    correct: "Minneapolis Lakers",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA player holds the record for most consecutive games with at least 30 points?",
    choices: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "James Harden",
      "Kobe Bryant",
    ],
    correct: "James Harden",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team was led by Jason Kidd in the early 2000s?",
    choices: [
      "Phoenix Suns",
      "New York Knicks",
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "New Jersey Nets",
    ],
    correct: "New Jersey Nets",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is one of the shortest NBA players in history?",
    choices: ["Kemba Walker", "Spud Webb", "Isiah Thomas", "Shane Larkin"],
    correct: "Spud Webb",
  },
];

export const mediumTF: TFQuestionType[] = [
  {
    question:
      "The three-point line is closer in FIBA basketball than in the NBA.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Miami Heat won back-to-back NBA Championships in 2012 and 2013.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The San Antonio Spurs are the only NBA team to have never drafted a player from outside of the United States.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Kobe Bryant was drafted by the Charlotte Hornets before being traded to the Los Angeles Lakers.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "The Chicago Bulls won six NBA Championships in the 1990s.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "Tim Duncan is the all-time leader in blocked shots in the NBA.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question: "LeBron James has won the NBA MVP award five times.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Golden State Warriors' home arena is called the 'Oracle Arena.'",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The NBA's shot clock was introduced in 1951 to speed up the game.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Miami Heat won their first NBA Championship in the 2005-2006 season.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Karl Malone is the fourth all-time leading scorer in NBA history.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Boston Celtics have won more NBA championships than any other team.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Michael Jordan played his entire NBA career with the Chicago Bulls.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The shot clock resets to 14 seconds on an offensive rebound in the NBA.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "Linsanity began against the New Jersey Nets",
    correct: "True",
  },
];
